Baiqiang Industry
Is Baiqiang Industry coming?
But this time
I think it's better if you don't take it
Can you earn a little bit?
Then you should call a taxi
You made the wrong call
That's not entirely wrong.
Where is your destination
We are a special
We can deliver whatever
the post office doesn't deliver.
Can send anything
by any means
wow absolutely
get expensive
wow I go
I'll leave it to you
How are you today? Did you get a lot?
Not much gain
Is it an emergency?
We are just a shipping company
You'll have to deal with that
on your own before shipping.
But if in transit
whatever happens
Our drivers will be held
accountable to the end
you don't need to worry
good good
my beer
- boss you again
- shh
yes of course
can you stop drinking my beer
Please send the client's
photo to this number
For details, please ask our driver
Then we will see you later
No drink driving
I have an appointment today
Boss, can you come out after a long time?
What kind of appointment do you have?
You have to have friends
before someone asks you out
bring it on
Go for a run tonight
Night allowance 15%
5%
15%
make a deal
here
here here
Brother, this is the car
what's the situation
Boy, open the door, you boy
I go
hateful
Why don't you open the door quickly?
Isn't this a girl movie?
Is it a girl movie?
Mom
It's a girl movie
It's not good at all
sorry bro
Can a girl film get things done?
If you don't go now, you won't
be able to get on the boat, bro
hateful
Going crazy
Isn't that Kim Jong-tae's sidekick?
If it can't be done, wait for me
Please fasten your seat belt
I wear a belt
how about here
Then I'll be charged an additional
60,000 won for a seat belt fine.
Hateful
hey I go
seat belt seat belt
OK
Stimulate
you bastard
parking
stop yourself
park me
parking
you give me a good time
do you want to drive in there
no no no
What should we do now
Oh, it's really on time, on time
Hey
Confirm your pay
where is your resume
What does it mean
tip?
This is not a tip
care for you
How do you come to work under me?
Except for the wine industry
This is the first time I want
to work with a girl like you
it's your honor
Give
Thank you
Take care, you'd better keep it
hello who is your boss
Asif
send me a cup of milk coffee
wow our Section Chief Jang
Sooner or later, I have to divide
the six or four points for you to adjust.
Right
Then it will be divided
into 50 to 50 from tomorrow.
I have that mind
It's not reality, it's just thoughts
The boss is meaningless if
he doesn't express his thoughts
hello five or five
That means we are partners
Then I can't call you Section
Chief Jang like I do now.
I should call you Representative Jang.
Also, do you think the
benefits are all in my pocket?
Rent reception fee
Company operations
understood
Don't talk to me if you're
not ready to adjust your split
Damn, the smoke didn't
even get through the trachea.
All in all, you won't listen
to the doctor even if you die
Boss, you have to live a hundred years.
You are my job
But how about my dinner party?
Let's eat roast beef Roast beef
what do you like to eat
tendon meat
beef loin
just mention it
Yeah
Some of these guys don't eat beef
do not eat pork
What did you eat to grow up?
When did we stop eating beef
It's India that doesn't eat beef
That guy is from Pakistan
That guy is from Bangladesh
Those two big brothers don't eat pork
How much does that beef cost?
These troublesome guys are
completely indistinguishable
Indians eat curry
That's Eun-Ha's
Who
- Section Chief Jang?
- Um
Relying on my own two brushes
The lawless Section Chief Jang?
Section Chief Jang, who prefers
home-cooked food to dinner parties?
Is my sister off work?
How did Section Chief
Jang become your sister?
Are you a family
Who are you dating?
Stinky boy don't eat
I want to eat it all by myself
soon to be
The shortest time in history to exceed
8 million viewers professional baseball
shocking news
Today's Kim Seong
Dragons player Lee Do Young
Held a press conference for
the Declaration of Conscience
The truth about the fake
professional baseball game revealed
hateful
where is it
Sites under investigation
for game manipulation…
Let's take a look at Lee Do
Young's press conference first.
Four bad balls at a time or
drop points in one inning...
hateful
A week ago…
Dad, you're on TV
what
Middleman accused in
Lee contestant's confession
is a former professional baseball player
proven This person entered the
entertainment industry after retiring early
Kim Doo-sik in his
activities as a TV personality
The middleman Kim not
only has the above behaviors
Also operated gambling sites for many years
Kim's collusion with public officials
now the focus of the investigation
Whoops how did they pick that photo?
I obviously have so many more
handsome photos of your dad
Right
I told you before, don't do this
Kim Seo-Won, have you
packed all your luggage?
Obviously didn't clean up at all
pack up
family
pig's trotter
Bayama
mountain
live octopus
wallet
Bag
gas mutation
I've never heard of such a word
Why
It was delicious today too
Like Subscribe Come on
Then we'll see you tomorrow bye bye
these puppies
Don't like anything subscribe
Damn, bad luck, I
really don't want to do it
I need ASMR when I do live streaming
Can't you be quiet, you bastards, be quiet?
One by one
-Hello
-OK
I told you before
good for you
OK
That please
When can I get on board?
Tomorrow night at 9:00 Pyeongtaek port
Pyeongtaek port tomorrow night at 9pm
cash received
do you have a car
yes I parked outside
wow awesome
are you going to drive your own car
Is that a taxi?
I wipe the taxi
Honey, you are so awesome
Dear
Did you know that among
those trying to smuggle
Ninety percent of them were
caught before they got on the boat
so what?
So what
I have one here
Special programs that
take you to your destination
really highly recommend
how much
two bundles of this
Not so many children
A total of 20 million won
How do you want me to ask you about it?
Don't you
help me find out
Of course I'll ask
OK
Subscribe Come on
hey, bring me the phone
What's up
Oh shit
who are you, what's the matter
I am Jesus
he is moses
all spread out
come on, let's fight
get me some paper
boss
why are you here
This is my first time since moving
Yes
I heard you went on vacation a while ago
no recent kid
If you don't go to English
training camp during vacation
something big
Wow, it seems that Macau also
has an English training camp.
That is because
When I came back, I transferred to Macau.
This is...
Boss, this is a present for you
Thank you
this is nothing
But why did you suddenly pack your bags?
Don't you watch the news
news?
Oops
It's hard to create
a situation like that...
Oh, it's Lee Do Young
If you want to have a direct impact,
you need at least 20 million won
Four bad balls at a time
or drop points in one inning
That way there will be less
pressure on the opponent
It will provide about 200
to 5 million won each time
I think
It was one of the two of you who did it.
I did not do that
I really have nothing to do with this
There is no security key in the safe
That, yesterday you
weren't Jean's representative
I let Kim represent
He said you asked him to pick it up
I really am
How much money is in our vault account
About 30 billion won
Do you know why you two
became co-representatives?
Because the representative Kim can
lobby on the side of the active players
no no no
After all, I'm also a big businessman.
Wrong fuck
It's because I can't trust the two of you
I want you two to develop
your own personal power
But you said I let Jin represent
Ask him to get the security key
Rabbit
hey shave
If I win the lottery, I
will believe what you say
Then you just disappear
completely and never show up
What if you don't win
miss
If you don't get it, think about it later
What are you doing, shaving?
I shave
boss
Boss, it's all up to me
I'll be honest with the
investigation when I go in
I will do anything for you
So please, just once
please forgive me this time
Do you smoke here?
Can not help
OK
This bastard is so timid
Kim Doo-sik
But bet your life
No, don't take it
Dad is calling again
I told you not to take it
hello gold representative
How dare you answer the phone
Really is
hey I see you are driving
I'll make a long story short
The hundreds of millions of won
operating expenses that you misappropriated
treat it as your pension
well done well done
that's what you deserve
you send me the security key
Anyway, only I know the password
You can't get that 30 billion won
Answer Me Kim Representative
Okay
I give you
As long as I get to a
place where I can't see you
I'll give it to you then
so don't come after me you bastard
Or I'll destroy that security key
You bastard
I see your condition is not very good.
You don't have to
come, or I'll find you faster
just wait for me
I'll pick you up right away
come on asshole
Then let's try
See if I lost my life or you lost my money
did you sleep well
Are you hungry?
So hot so hot
chubby
chubby mom go out
You are at home and look at home
Mom worked so hard to feed my little chubby
Tell your mother a safe journey
Come on, today will be smooth too
hurry up
Ouch you little bastard
I'm leaving
Thanks for your hard work
Damn, this chassis is scratched
Sister, are you driving fatigued?
That's why I have to
go to the scene with you.
Itchy skin again?
Stop talking nonsense
install me a front camber
Feels bad when turning
Yes sir
- Section Chief Jang
- coming
go to seoul on business
Pyeongtaek Port 9 PM
Pyeongtaek port?
This is Im Ki-Bang's list.
I said it, that guy is
dirty, don't take his orders
The pay is good
If you think it's dirty, just
take a pat and clean it up
My heart is like a mirror
Let him call a chauffeur to fool him.
Hey Hey hey
Would you still come to us
if you could call a chauffeur?
It's all for a reason.
I'm not interested in
other people's reasons
It is for these reasons
that we can make a living.
Five to five
how can suddenly
five to five
make a deal
Okay, I'm only in charge of delivery
If the package is not good, it
will be rejected, but I will just leave.
Good good
Do as you like, Representative Han
Uijeongbu Hope Ballpark Pickup at 8pm
Delivered to Pyeongtaek Port at 9:00
This is the client's photo
There is another passenger
Have a spare car in Pyeongtaek port
The rest will be taken locally
When faced with a dilemma
When in a dilemma,
choose public transportation
Calls only use 2G
The main entrance to the park is here
small exit here
There are two
The client is around here
If Chief Jang you were here
Where is the pick-up location?
Here it is
Go around the island without
getting stabbed in the back
That's right
If someone is following
Even if they rush in from here
Also easy to throw away
You can get out immediately
from the outer ring
OK
But what is this
at the crossroads
It's just a lighter
stop stop stop
You, you always get lost
drive safely
OK
Boss
she forgot this
throw the last ball
last ball
Where is he
Really, this simple guy
I got it, I went first
Seo-Won
Although Dad failed to get eight wins
But you're going to win 18 wins and 20 wins
then into the MLB
remember?
Didn't you let me play baseball?
Don't you hate baseball
how can I hate baseball
it's baseball that hates me
It must be the car
This kid doesn't run as fast as I imagined.
Dad
how did it start
hey come out
Du-Sik
Do you do it yourself or we smash it
Why don't you answer my call?
Du-Sik
Seo-Won, look at dad, look at dad
Seo-Won
Seo-Won, you must take this
- This bastard
- Seo-Won 6162
The three-way road at the entrance to
the baseball stadium, you remember?
You go there and find the car
with the license plate number 6162
That's the car that came to pick us up
Let's chat when we're done eating
you take your phone away
If you can't remember, you keep
checking the text message to confirm
Confirmed, turn off immediately
I put it in your pocket
when are you coming
daddy will find you soon
I'll use this to call you.
Right
Hey
what's the matter, don't cry
what do men care about
courage
remember?
Let's go, let's go, let's go
chubby
where did it go
Did you have meal
get out, brat
come here
Oh shit
come here fuck
Come here, Cao Qingbi
I go to this guy
damn it
I've played baseball before, so what?
Is that how you fight?
Damn it's a foul
Hey, didn't I give you a chance?
Make you drain the lives of people like you
Didn't I make you a representative?
But why are you sticking a knife in my back
Does it hurt to be stabbed in the back?
Hey Du-Sik
I really ask you one last time
where is the security key
Where is it, boy, tell the truth
hmm where is it
I ate it
what did you say
Open my stomach and take it
good to know
come quickly
so slow today
hey go find
hello there
open the door
help
Come over here
-found it
- help please
come over
Open the door, please
It's 6162, right?
Hey catch him catch him
hi parking
I told you to stop one stop
parking
damn
what the fuck
no security key
should be with the child
I just got here
Doo-sik waved when he saw my car
Must be waiting to prepare to escape
Come out
The woman who took
the child away is a master
is that woman
Well, it's a woman
hello, call the head of the room
Hey
I'm doing laundry
okay, got it
Wait for me
Hey
My name is Kim SeoWon
you left this
don't follow me you go yours
There's a subway station over there.
Would you like to take the subway?
I have nowhere to go
None of my business
What if those hooligans keep chasing me?
Tell the police
Dad won't let me go to the police
Auntie, didn't you come to save me?
Hmm no
But you obviously saved me just now
I'm here to make money
I have money
hello ok
Dad said he would call me
Just accompany me to that time
Hello Section Chief Jang
can you explain
A delivery accident occurred
damn it
Where is the client with you?
No only children
What a mess
In this case, it cannot be returned
So didn't I say don't take it?
Damn that kid Im Ki-Bang
Get out
I'm going to cut off the line of
contact on Im Ki-Bang's side.
You can also withdraw
Did you get the delivery fee?
Not yet
He seems to have put
some money on the child
OK, how about the labor fee?
Put him in the proper place
and get the money back
wait
- Hey
- My name is Kim Seo-Won
do you have a mother
grandma or grandpa
no
Neither did the aunt or uncle?
Do you have friends
Aunt, do you have
hmm a lot
No one has a boss, can you help me find it?
As soon as possible
do it
There's a place for kids over there
put him there
Then we're done shipping
I have moles here too
Do you want to play word solitaire?
Word Solitaire
Sleep
cheapskate
what am I doing
oh, it's awesome
But it's a foul to say a sentence, auntie
have to say words
Hey
My name is Kim Seo-Won
don't call me auntie
what should you be called
- don't call
-Humph
Is it the Boss Baek?
You are far away
I am Seo-Won
Yes Se-Won, let's go with uncle
do you want to eat
have you been starving your child
oops
Ouch, eat slowly
Boss Baek is fine.
Long time no see him
what are you doing there
Why are you afraid we
will sell chewing gum?
Oops, can't do those lately
Now we are all doing legal things too...
What are you eating so soon?
Give you another
oops
Let's go now and say goodbye to my sister
thanks
Bring a good to the Boss Baek
oops
- Is delivery finished?
- Yes
OK, hard work
Did you confirm the delivery fee?
Confirm later
don't count?
Do you have to count now?
Didn't you say it was given by a child?
Hurry up and count
enough
why are you angry?
How can you not confirm
the delivery fee once?
What's the matter today boy
You know what I count?
Damn
How can I do this to a child
where is the child
Go shit, haven't come out yet
is he constipated
The leader is bleeding here
what blood?
Yes
Hey, nothing is scattered, scattered
Body of Gambling Site Middleman Kim Doo-sik
Found at the scene of a baseball
stadium fire Have you heard?
Yes Yes
someone reported that
car seen after fire
Escaped from the entrance
to the baseball stadium
The car is an old BMW
This is the same type of
car reported by witnesses
before the fire
Video taken on the road
near the baseball stadium
The license plate is the license plate of the confiscated
vehicle that has been put on hold for no reason
Cars are completely different
That is, a set car
Kim Doo-sik was killed after that.
Hello next
There's a child in the passenger
seat that just didn't exist, right?
That's Kim Doo-sik's son Kim Seo-won
Deck cars with confiscated license plates
Kim Doo-sik who was killed
That is to say
the guy in the baseball cap
It's killing Kim Doo-sik
And the biggest suspect in
abducting Kim Seo-Won, right?
Come here at 10:10 now
It's been two hours
Two hours is enough for them to deliver.
Gotta catch
Find me all the nearby roads and highways
Find me right away and get it back, okay?
-Yes
hey, spread out
- big brother
- Um
Is it okay to arrest them in public?
Hey Sang-Hoon
Not 3 million won but 30 billion won
Three million won can be
earned as long as you work hard
But 30 billion won...
Oh, you gotta do it well
Fight for your life and do it well, boy
Are you leaving me again?
I'm not going to buy something.
Can this be believed?
Aunt
Is life so tiring?
What's so tiring
I'm hungry
so many things
Hey, you have to describe it well
how does it taste
nice and warm
Does warmth mean taste?
Hey you taste and tell me
that
May I ask who is Mr. Im Ki-Bang?
What's your business…
What to do
damn it
hey, stop it
hey I tell you to stop
He still has to answer
the question, how come
You really don't know how to restrain
who are you
he can answer
This bastard is really...
Chief Jang called me
Stinky girl, are you crazy?
Why are you always acting arbitrarily?
Hey, are you being targeted by flies now?
Be careful
If something catches up with you,
take the headquarters in as well.
Then we're done, you know?
Chief Jang, I forgive you
come back soon, you know...
Got it, I'll send this over and go back
Hurry up, finish it, finish it soon
Did you send someone to pick him up?
No
I only prepare passport and boat
They are a special delivery
Professional shippers who deliver by piece
- Shipper?
- Right
where are they now
every delivery
They all only tell me a black number
I just said I didn't come to the boat
I called and found it didn't work
That is to say
You have nothing to tell me now, do you?
No, I really hurt
car
car what?
They carry a dozen license
plates with each delivery
If it is exposed, it will change
the license plate or change the car
then throw off the tracking
uh stop what you're doing now
Check to see if your
vehicle has been stolen
From the suspects caught
at the time of the theft
Screen people with physical characteristics
Ouch, you hit so hard, you stinky boy
go to the hospital quickly
don't worry about the dog
what to say
go to the hospital
Anyway, you kid is really not overdone.
Found it at Mega
Supermarket in Seokgyo-dong
we're tracking vehicle movement
Do you want to arrest immediately
after confirming the location?
Well, of course they
will be arrested, but...
That girl is professional,
you have to be careful
The deceased was
recently under investigation
In connection with the
illegal gambling website case
And the wanted Kim Doo-sik
except for burns
A sunken skull and multiple
fractures were also found
and abdominal stab wounds
So in order to find the exact cause
of death Preparing for an autopsy
Unlawful death of suspect Kim Doo-sik...
my dad is dead
There's a woman with a baby
at what date
don't move
where did you go
no
Not in the bathroom
Damn in another room
do not Cry
Hey Kim Seo-Won, stop crying
If you want to live, don't cry
Now you know
go
Are we someone in the police?
How is this going
we want to check
open the door
I almost missed it, sorry.
Send this to me and it's over
get off work
Didn't receive the delivery fee?
Would you like me to give it to you?
Police salary is not enough
Oh, good eyesight
It's a shame it's just shipping
His dad stole my stuff
He seems to have taken
that thing by accident
I just need to get my stuff
after getting it
After that... I'm a little worried too.
What can be done
He saw when his dad died
My situation is also very difficult.
Hey little, do you still
remember Uncle's face?
Will you drive
Little Uncle will pick you
up soon and wait for me
Is this what that uncle is looking for?
Give this to him and he
won't chase after him?
Got it, I heard it, calm down, calm down
Scared me a little bit
Is it inconvenient to talk now?
No, say it, say it
What are you saying about the police?
The police want to investigate the
identity of a person said to be a suspect
The boss asked you to confirm quickly
Oops
hateful
I can't drive
who is that man
Hey, are the identification results out?
Why so long
The fingerprints do not appear to
be in the existing offender database
I have never been caught so far.
Who is she
Name Jang Eun-Ha Age 28
No family, no criminal record
Born in Pingcheng, South Ping An
looks like a defector
I'm like, why is it so awesome?
What is your current address?
Ominous place of residence
In addition to knowing that it is
a red molecule Nothing to gain
Is it because of lack of strength?
Hello
You are…
I haven't had a spy recently,
so I've been very busy, right?
The National Intelligence Service
even intervenes in the police affairs
leisure is not idle
To be honest, we also find it troublesome
But if no matter
If it is rumored that the National Intelligence Service
is ineffective in managing North Korean defectors
something like that
That's more trouble
If you deal with these red
criminals in the first place
There's no such thing, right?
That is to say
So we have the feeling that we
need to tie the bell to untie the bell
I want to help you catch the suspect
I was the one who checked Jang
Eun-Ha for defecting from North Korea.
She is in a family who
defected from North Korea
All the family died and escaped alone
let me see
hey, murder, kidnapping
what a big deal
keep it simple
You are worrying about how
to find Jang Eun-Ha, ​​right?
Let's be your beacon
Just follow the light to catch Jang Eun-Ha.
How can you help me
police?
If you know the police are
chasing you, your boss will kill you.
Do as he pleases
If you want to kill or cut
him, let him pick us up now
Uncle, let me tell you a
number, you can memorize it
0118 what is this
my home password
that... sister
You suddenly take the
initiative to make me a little panic.
Little fat let you feed the little fat
Bye
OK
Not bad
Who is the chubby?
Was it raised by my aunt?
Um
Do you live with the cat
Cute, right
so fierce looking
hey isn't it
So cute, take a look
I'm going to mom
send me to mom
Didn't you say you don't have a mother?
Dad means no
But there are
do you know where
It's a lot
But how do you know your mom is in here?
I've called all
And then did someone say she's your mother?
Not the only one who didn't say anything
And kept crying
Put that time on the phone
number displayed on the base station
download all
When will it be confirmed?
Why do you want to confirm each one?
There shouldn't be many 2G phones in there.
Hello, are you a Park Ji-sung customer?
We are a flower delivery
service hotline that delivers love
24 Hours Cupid Flowers
found it
Just exited the Seoul toll gate
Now head south along the Gyeongbu Line
We can reduce the range to
within a radius of 500 meters
I will continue to send real-time locations
- Team Leader Cao
- what
Let us know as soon as you find someone
come on
hey found that woman
Let's take the police over there
and deal with me before that.
About to reach the destination
destination reached
I'm going to bring your
mother over here, just stay here
Wait a moment
this is for you
You won't lose it when you take this
Don't open the door for anyone
Feel sorry
I did have a baby when I followed Doo-sik
But premature birth did not meet
like last year
I did receive a rare
call from Brother Doozhi.
I heard the child's voice
suddenly excited
tears fall
It's really a misunderstanding
Are you really not Seo-Won's mother?
No I said no
you are so stubborn
Seo-Won is so pitiful
All he can rely on now is his mother
Then why did you promise
him to see his mother?
I heard that the people who killed
Brother Du-Sik were looking for children
Who will you go to next besides Dad?
Could it be mom
The child should grow up, right?
Are you obedient
You don't need to know that much
Didn't I tell you to
wait for me in the car?
I am sorry
let's go
what about mom
She's not your mother, you're mistaken
deceive
I'm going to ask her
why did you break my phone
Why did you break the phone
That's right, she's your mother
But she said she doesn't
want to see you, understand?
She said she doesn't want to be your mother
I don't need you anymore
You're here to make money, right?
Take this with me, I'll go back by myself
whatever
after you
Aunt
Get down, get it up and take it to the car
aunt aunt
Aunt
do not move
what's the situation
are you alright
sit in front
fasten your seat belt
how does she drive
Aunt
aunt aunt
Are you really rich?
Ouch god
Hey
finally got it
looks like you are busy
Where is our team leader busy?
Of course the police came out to arrest
the murderer, what else could they do?
Fortunately
I thought I told you the location in
real time but you didn't catch anyone
I was worried that
something happened to you
thank you for your kindness
Anyway, it's a long story
After all, the plan doesn't change quickly.
By the way, that Jang Eun-Ha
Doesn't seem like a trafficker
what do you mean
I have heard eyewitness testimony
It turned out that the child turned
back to the passerby for help
Take the injured Jang
Eun-Ha and take the car away
Is Jang Eun-Ha really a human trafficker?
So just grab it and show it to you
I mean give me the evidence you have...
Forget it, the lighthouse lights are off.
Let's go our separate ways
if there is anything else to say
Please also send an
official letter to hang up
what does this bastard mean
damn stinky woman
brat
hey can you talk
Just hold on, it's over soon
Hey, you're finally loyal to death
Do you still have connections at the
Gyeonggi Regional Police Agency?
Yes
You go and check the evidence
at the scene of Kim Doo-sik's death
I went to see where Jang
Eun-Ha disappeared at the end
That's a long distance, okay?
Of course, what else can I do?
Where is the listing for the
car she originally drove from?
Gangneung
It was the car that came to
the hotel and drove to Daejeon
Listings are different
One is Incheon and the other is…
However, all of them are vehicles that have
been sold off due to unauthorized listing. right
you check out those outlets
Yes
Hey
How can you spend so
much money on this broken car
Are you burning too much money?
Where did you lose your
car keys that you paid for?
You don't just get lost all day
Before it is in place, I
need to enter two fingers
so inexperienced
Then you do it
stop turn right
wow good
- why don't you drive
-Yes
You can't sit next to those short legs
where are we going
Have you been to Busan?
No
Great
After your call goes
unanswered and beeps...
Hey
Boss Baek
hey where are you
what are you doing all day
I can't find anyone who
can take care of my children
- guess
- guess what
are you bringing it here?
Come over
what
The delivery location cannot
be changed or returned
It's been trickier than ever, isn't it?
The kid is right next to
me, take a picture for me
take a picture
Didn't you say the other
party was a policeman?
I can't be safe here
Send the child away as soon as it arrives
- I prepare a passport
- sit down
We've got to do this anyway, right?
Deliver responsibly
Chief Jang, are you listening?
Yes of course
stand up
so dirty
you are dirtier
stand up
I'm going to shoot
Hey
have a cup of coffee here
Miss Jang Eun-Ha
Do you have a boyfriend
why
nothing
who is your ideal type
I don't know I didn't think about those
Think about it now
person who doesn't pee his pants
Don't talk nonsense, okay?
You don't want to listen
but…
What happened again
Why did you take a picture of me just now?
Needed for going abroad
Who is going abroad
you
are you together too
Do not
Why didn't I go to your house?
Big brother found the place of sale
All three cars are sold in Busan
The company that recycles
vehicles is called Baiqiang Industry
Should be a scrap car recycling company
brat
Throwing things as a cop
Retire anyway
ok go get your pension
sister
Hey, where did this shit come from?
Take it easy. This is a
car worth 20 million won.
20 million won
How to say
don't know ask him
Why is this car worth 20 million won?
Came so fast
It just looks like we have to stop
let me see
Baek Yeon-Hee
Yeok Bong-Hee
what does this read
Ji-Ho
Which one do you like
what do you like
your pseudonym
I have a name
I know your name is Kim Seo-Won
But a lot of people have two names
you know EXO
They also have two names
Yes, there is a girlfriend
I don't have a girlfriend
I'm talking about girl
groups called girlfriends
They also have two names
keep going
Seo-Won will also take that car
Do you want to go by car?
Don't you want to go abroad?
Um
There's a big ship with that kind of car
It looks like you haven't been seated
Seo-Won, you just need
to hold the steering wheel
Then sleep five nights
and go to my hometown
When you get there my
dad can take care of you
We Seo-Won will have to eat
curry every day from now on.
President
OK Ji-Ho, let's decide Ji-Ho
How
I'll use this to show off
when the child is gone
let him go far
That's what his dad meant
That's why I sent it here
I'll take care of the aftermath
You clean up the aftermath
Seeing how you're doing
things is still a long way off.
Do you remember
big brother
stay safe
Hey
I will have a pension
That amount is too much
So I want to spend it with you
how are you interested?
What should we do bro
help me find someone
no no no
find a person and a child
will you come to see me
It depends on how you do it
If you don't have a
boyfriend by then, auntie
how about I be your boyfriend
what happened to you just now
nothing
Be sure to look carefully and let
us know immediately if you find it
OK
Found here
Hey Du-Sik
I really ask you one last time
where is the security key
Where is it, boy, tell the truth
I ate it
Open my stomach and take it
Turns out he wasn't after a murderer
He's a murderer himself
this bastard
Where is Cao Qingbi now?
After passing the Busan
Expressway toll station, I can't track it.
I know I will go to Busan first
Hand-Pulled Noodle
noodle
shaving
salamander
salamander fish
you are too cunning
Two hours after the transaction, you
can leave Hong Kong and come here
ok please take care of him
The car was brought
Can't hurt the driver
Do you know who I am
gangster
or the police
I have both jobs
whatever you do
Gotta let me get off work, get off work
hide here
You absolutely can't come out, you know?
You just need to answer my three questions
and I'll let you off work immediately
where is this kid
Where is Jang Eun-Ha
do you want to die
So you have to keep your eyes open
how to use The third-rate,
the reds, the illegal overstayers
For those of us who do small business
Labor costs are an issue
that cannot be ignored
That's true
Jang Eun-Ha, ​​this child can work well
I have also used many drivers
But no one can control it
Sometimes I can beat the old me
blue out of blue
When I saw that girl for the first time
I'm going to the North
Korean border to pick her up
The little girl's film is covered in blood
But it was me who was hurt
Boss, you were once red
I am from Seoul
when I was doing business in russia
worked odd jobs
Bringing Reds Fleeing
North Korea to South Korea
part time
Boss, you are also a famous person.
So where is she
my god new face
hey black
You tell me
Jang Eun-Ha, ​​where is
she and that little one?
Don't speak Korean?
Where is Jang Eun-Ha
talk to me
money
I'll give you money tell me
I give you money, very big money
get out of the asshole
get out
this kid
You speak Korean very well.
Asif
be honest with me
stop
I tell you to stop
I don't even know where they are
wait until I finish that
I will contact you
but
do you know where is
what you are looking for
what am I looking for
Are you looking for a bank security key?
I give you the bank security key
just leave us alone
this is my condition
Where
Wu Gang
yes, Sir
Brother, there is a combination lock here
Fingerprint recognition
pull him out
How painful is it to pull it out?
Pull it out at once
By the way, how much can you share?
Looking at you working so hard, you should
be able to drop hundreds of millions of won.
How can a mere few hundred
million won make me die?
Boss
Asif you boy
Why don't you run away?
Is this what bro is looking for?
Hurry up and find that kid and make an end
Whoever finds me first will
give a bounty of 100 million won
go find
you say
I just received a call that a gunshot was
heard in the direction of Gijang-gun, Busan.
It is a waste car processing
plant called Baiqiang Industry.
The boss is called Baek Iron and Steel
Wait a minute, you just said Baek steel
right there
The broker who brought Jang Eun-Ha
to North Korea was called Baek Gang
Immediately notify the Busan
Police Station and request support
I found you 100 million won
big brother
I said I'd find it soon
Hello little
Uncle said he would find you soon, right?
What happened
what's the situation
what are you doing
go turn on the lights
Is Jang Eun-Ha you?
Run
run fast
stinky bitch
kill you
elder brother
How are you
Seo-Won
elder brother
Asif
brother is still there
Brother was seriously injured
wait a minute
let go of the child
stop it, okay?
Do you smoke
Damn you forgot your cigarette
You are desperately trying to find death
Everything else is trying to survive
Didn't you escape to
Korea to change your fate?
Who is this little one of yours?
So hard for him
Auntie, are you alright?
Do you look like I'm fine?
I drive too
Fighting is also me
what kind of boyfriend are you
what did this girl say
Don't worry about Kim Seo-Won
Let's go with auntie
Oh shit
Are you showing me a sad scene?
Jang Eun-Ha
so-called life
should go alone
separate
Auntie please help Auntie
please save auntie
take him away
please
please please
Miss Jang Eun-Ha
How are you
I'm very good
Our class has transferred a new partner
I changed schools
This time, I transferred to a school
farther away than my original school.
Very uncomfortable at first
Made a lot of friends now
Su-Wan often plays together
because they live together
Now I live in Happy Garden Nursery Home
- The food here is delicious and the teacher is also very good. I am very satisfied.
- Let's go
Okay
And the uncle driver of our school bus
Driving is messed up
But auntie, you can drive
- By the way, Chubby has brother Asif to take care of him.
- Eat more
so don't worry
and
just write it here I'll write to you
next time, I won't write this time
Bye then
uncle
Aunt
Get in the car, I'll take
you there, get in the car
Let's drop by a place